And now it's time for the big up let down goes to the control alt delete button at CNN.com.
They posted this article about South Carolina finishing the season undefeated after whooping
Iowa in the championship game.
And then the picture they posted was of Iowa, the losers.
Now the Caucasia of that, the caucasity of that was noted by the internets and they was
not having it.
They dragged CNN like a mop over big mama's kitchen floor.
And you know what CNN did?
They said, whoop, whoop, switch that up.
Now there is a pick of the winning team.
And guess what?
It's a bunch of black girls.
If you do better from the jump, you ain't got to get jumped.
That's how that goes.
Today's let down goes to duct tape for not holding together that Boeing plane that recently
had to make an emergency landing.
another Boeing plane can Ford start building planes because I want a plane that's tough.
Now we know duct tape that you're what the former CEO and higher ups at Boeing have been
relying on this whole time.
We know that it certainly isn't competence and leadership.
It's not that we're concerned about public safety.
Ain't that either.
At this point, duct tape, you are all we got.
And you just, you're not doing your job.
So I'm going to need you to get more about your ducking with your tape.
All right.
I'm concerned.